You've been working with a predict state function that takes
我们之前一直在使用一个预测状态函数
in a current state and some change in time, dt.
利用当前状态和时间变化 dt
And it outputs a new state estimate based on a constant velocity motion model.
并且基于恒定速度运动模型输出新的状态估计
It turns out a constant velocity model is actually a good simple model to use,
事实证明 恒定速度模型实际上是一个很好的简单模型
especially if changes in time are very small.
时间变化非常小时效果更好
Now, to track the state of a car over time as the car moves,
现在 要在汽车移动时跟踪汽车的状态
you have to repeatedly call this function
你必须重复调用这个函数
passing in new state estimates at each time step.
在每个时间步长得到新的状态估计
So as an example,
例如
let's say we have this initial state at
假设初始状态为
position x equals zero and velocity equals 50 meters per second.
位置 x 即零米位置 速度等于 50 米每秒
I'll put these two values into a list,
我将这两个值放在列表中
our initial state, and I'll print them out.
初始状态列表中 然后输出这个结果
So, the initial state is x equals zero and velocity equals 50 meters per second.
因此 初始状态为x等于零 速度等于50米/秒
Next, I want to know the next state after two seconds have passed.
接下来 我想知道两秒钟后的下一个状态
So, I'll use my predict state function passing in
我会使用我的预测状态函数导入
the initial state in the two-second time difference and I'll call this state,
两秒钟的时间差的初始状态 我将这个状态称为
est1, for the first state estimate and I'll print out this result.
est1 用于初始状态估计 我将输出这个结果
Our position, x, is now at 100 meters and the velocity remains 50 meters per second.
我们的位置 x 现在在100米 速度保持在每秒50米
Then, say another three seconds, have passed.
然后 假设又过去了三秒钟
I'll call The predict state function again.
我将再次调用预测状态函数
This time, I'll pass in our latest state estimate, state_est1,
这一次 我会导入最新的状态估计 state_est1
and a three-second time difference and I'll print out this value.
和三秒钟的时差 我会输出这个值
Our position is now 250 meters and our velocity remains constant at 50 meters per second.
我们的位置现在是250米 速度保持恒定在每秒50米
What about after three more seconds?
再过三秒钟呢？
I'll have to pass in our latest state estimate, state_est2,
我必须导入我们最新的状态估计 state_est2
and three more seconds in time difference and I'll print out the result.
和三秒钟的时差 我将输出这个值
As you can see, we're basically calling the same line of code over and over
因此 我们实际上是一遍又一遍地调用同一行代码
again but modifying the state input to be the latest state estimate.
不过是将状态输入修改为最新的状态估计而已
This repetition is tedious at best and it's bad code.
这种重复很无聊 因此这代码写得并不好
As a programmer, you should always try to avoid unnecessary repetition.
作为程序员 你应该始终尽量避免不必要的重复
Wouldn't it be nice to just tell a car to move and
让一辆车移动
have its state update automatically as it moved,
并且在移动时自动更新状态 岂不是要比
as opposed to writing the same line of code manually
手动写入相同代码
keeping track of the state over and over again?
并重复跟踪汽车位置更好？
Well, we can automatically keep track of state with the help of objects.
我们可以在对象的帮助下自动跟踪状态